You're braver than you believe. Stronger than you
seem. And smarter than you think.
Pooh's Grand Adventure: The Search for Christopher Robin is a
animation, family, adventure film directed by Karl Geurs.
Pooh gets confused when Christopher Robin leaves him a note to say
that he has gone back to school after the holidays.
So Pooh, Piglet, Tigger, Eeyore and Rabbit go in search of
Christopher Robin which leads to a big adventure.
Winnie the Pooh / Skullasaurus growls / Tigger
(singing) (voice), played by Jim Cummings.
Piglet (voice), played by John Fiedler.
Rabbit (voice), played by Ken Sansom.
Tigger (voice), played by Paul Winchell.
Eeyore (voice), played by Peter Cullen.
Christopher Robin (voice), played by Brady Bluhm.
Pooh's Grand Adventure: The Search for Christopher Robin is a 1997 American direct-to-video animated
musical adventure comedy-drama film co-written, co-produced, and directed by Karl Geurs.
The film follows Winnie the Pooh and his friends on a journey to find and
rescue their friend Christopher Robin from the "Skull".
Along the way, the group confront their own insecurities throughout the search, facing and conquering them in a series of
events where they are forced to act beyond their own known limits, thus discovering their true potential.
Unlike the film's predecessors, this film is an entirely
original story, not based on any of A.
Milne's classic stories.
The film explores themes of cartoon, hand drawn animation,
cartoon animal, winnie the pooh, courage.